[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
When we were little,
you always scrimped and saved
to buy me food.
Eat more.
Sixth Master,
what do we do now?
Zhang Dancheng told me this
because he wants to use me
to kill Sect Master.
Why don't I just kill them all?
Keep them alive.
After I kill Sect Master,
I'm going to make them
take the fall.
Scared?
Sixth Master,
you picked me out of a pile of corpses.
My life is yours.
Whoever you want to kill...
I, Fan Yifei, will be the first to strike.
Let's go.
Bring Shangguan Chengming along.
[A Prophet]
[Episode 23]
Bringing you two back means
I've completed Sect Master's task.
After tonight,
the act you and your mentor put on
can come to an end.
After I kill Sect Master,
I'll let you go.
I may be a scoundrel,
but I keep my word.
[Equally Adept at the Pen and the Sword]
What is it?
I know everything.
Know what?
You killed my mother.
Yes.
You've been lying to me all these years.
Why?
I felt like it.
Then today,
let's settle this score.
How do we settle it?
With your life.
Wait!
Since it's the end,
you should at least let me say my last words.
Go on.
I only have one request.
I want to hear you call me
Dad.
Then I can die in peace.
Call me Dad.
Go on.
Say it.
What's wrong?
Can't say it?
Or do you think I don't deserve it?
No way.
Is it that hard?
I raised you since you were little.
I sent you to a private school to learn to read,
hired Flying Dagger Li from Shanxi
to teach you martial arts,
and let you live a decent life.
I remember that when you first joined the sect, you were about 10.
Those Batous bullied you,
stole all the food in your bowl, leaving you with
only steamed cornbread to eat.
You hid behind this house and cried.
When I witnessed it,
without hesitation,
I gave them 10 lashes each.
From then on, you had meat, endless meat,
every day.
I made that happen.
For this alone,
shouldn't you call me Dad?
There's more.
When you were 15,
you had a huge boil on your butt,
as big as an egg.
No doctor could cure it.
I had no choice
but to cut it open with a knife,
put my mouth on your butt cheek,
and suck the pus out.
I sucked it for 7 days,
before you got better.
You told me not to tell anyone.
I knew you were embarrassed,
so I didn't breathe a word to anyone.
You even said,
"Master,
you treat me better than my own mother."
Even with this,
you still can't call me Dad?
Say it.
Dad.
Louder.
Dad!
Good!
You can still call me Dad!
Thank you!
You still want to kill me!
You ingrate!
You'd have starved to death without me!
Even if you lived,
you'd just be some lousy fisherman in a seaside village.
I killed your mother
to cut off your attachments,
so you could start anew!
And you still want to kill me?
Dad...
Go.
Get my shoe back.
Come.
Put it on for me.
Why couldn't you just
make it easy on yourself?
Now it's my turn to ask you.
Any last words?
Mother,
why do I feel...
so wronged
inside?
I taught you:
to kill,
you must be ruthless
and swift.
You just think too much.
Did you really think I wouldn't know
what you've been plotting
behind my back?
Heavy is my mantle of leadership.
There's no hurry.
I'll personally escort you onto the stage
and let you put on a one-man show.
Take him away.
You, stay.
See that?
Are you scared?
I am.
From now on,
you are him:
the Sixth Batou.
Thank you, Master.
Notify the Batous to gather in the ancestral hall.
Sixth Batou is dead.
He died because of you.
Back then, you bribed Lu Qinhai
to kill Master Swindler's mother.
You kept it from him for so many years.
When Master Swindler learned of the truth,
you silenced him.
This is your venerable sect master.
Shut up!
It was Sect Master who saved Master Swindler
and buried his mother back then.
Brothers,
it goes without saying how well
Sect Leader has treated you.
I believe you all know it in your hearts.
Don't let this rogue's nonsense
cause friction within the sect!
Baichuan,
calm down.
Sit.
I've survived
so many years amid rumors. People have said
all kinds of things about me.
When we were young,
some even said I killed the old sect master.
Those who say these things
simply want to revolt against Tianxiang Sect.
What's more terrifying is
that there are our own people involved.
I know very well that
it's more than just one or two.
But don't worry.
As long as I sit on this throne,
I won't let the century-old foundation of Tianxiang Sect
go up in flames.
Master.
Senior!
Master!
What's wrong?
Master, what's wrong?
Master.
The tea is poisoned.
Lock Shangguan Chengming up!
Yes!
Master.
Senior, are you okay?
Are you alright, Master?
Quick, go brew some alum soup
to detoxify me.
No one follow me.
Let me meditate and channel my qi alone
to try to purge the poison.
Careful, Master.
I'll go right away.
Old man.
You still have to rely on me when it matters.
I know this place well.
How did you escape from Fan Yifei?
Those small fry under him
can't trap me, the Tongbei Spinning Top.
And Chengming warned me
to drink less.
He doesn't know
it takes a sea of booze to get me buzzed.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Where's Chengming?
Who's there?
I'm your father!
Stop!
Mentor.
The police tipped Sect Master off in advance.
Fan Yifei also turned against us.
They're trying to pin Master Swindler's death
on me
and accuse me of mutiny.
Done.
Leave the premises now.
Okay.
Feiyan,
forget about your lover.
Shangguan Chengming is absolutely
done for this time.
Instead of worrying about Master's health,
you're here being sarcastic.
Where are you going?
To find a doctor for Sect Master.
Should I just stand here
doing nothing like you?
Stop right there!
No one can leave the premises
until Sect Master comes out.
Senior.
The medicine is here.
Senior?
Senior!
Senior.
Somebody!
Anybody!
Come quickly!
Senior.
What's wrong with Master? Master!
Master!
Master.
This...
Senior.
Second Brother.
Senior,
trust that I'll avenge you.
I promise.
Eldest Master,
those two have been let go.
Send this news
to the other Batous.
Sect Master is dead.
The priority is to set up the funeral altar.
Tell everyone that
whatever it is,
we'll talk at the funeral.
Yes, Eldest Master.
[Honored Ancestor and Leader, Zhou Xingsi]
Eldest Brother,
the time has come.
Eldest Master,
Feiyan isn't here.
Let's wait for her.
Wait for her?
She was the closest to Shangguan Chengming.
Sect Master is dead, yet there is no sign of her.
Do you still not realize
who killed Sect Master by now?
Sect Master died an unjust death.
Shouldn't we let him rest in peace first?
The Chief Batou is right!
By the order of the founder,
the heroic soul of Zhou Xingsi,
the 24th Sect Master of Tianxiang Sect,
returns to a divine place of rest!
This soul is a loyal martyr of Tianxiang,
with towering righteousness.
May the Lord of the Underworld show mercy
and decree his swift reincarnation.
Gathering from all across the land to mourn,
we burn incense to honor our leader!
Sect Master met such a cruel fate,
yet Shangguan Chengming is nowhere to be found.
What an absolute dishonor to our Tianxiang Sect.
Today, we
swear a blood oath to
bring that evil scoundrel
back to the sect!
To the disloyal and treacherous...
-behold this lotus! -Behold this lotus!
I was with Sect Master the longest.
And you're next after me, right?
Say, were we blind
or just completely stupid
to ever trust Shangguan Chengming?
He was Sect Master's blessing in his later years.
At that age,
who wouldn't hope for a son?
That's true.
I heard that some people
in the sect have been wanting to flip the tables for a while.
It's just a few unseasoned punks
wagging their tongues.
Your loyalty to Sect Master
is obvious to all.
I just want
to lead a simple
and peaceful life.
I don't want
anything else.
A peaceful life is good.
I want a peaceful life too.
But
Sect Master put so much effort
into establishing this foundation,
only to leave just like that.
I...
As his junior,
shouldn't I protect the empire he built
even if it costs me my life?
Eldest Master,
I'm not good with subtleties.
Just give it
to me straight.
Alright.
Fill Second Master's cup.
Huaiyi,
there are some things I can't spell out
in the ancestral hall.
I know you like Feiyan.
But at a critical moment like this,
I advise you
to keep your hands clean.
I can't believe
Shangguan Chengming
really killed Sect Master.
You think it was him too?
To prevent Sect Master
from killing his mentor,
that hypocrite struck first
to kill the Sect Master,
and then fled.
There's no way
Shangguan Chengming is the killer.
It's not him?
If not him,
who else could it be?
Think about it.
The killer struck right after
Zhang Dancheng returned.
Isn't it obvious they're framing Shangguan Chengming?
This person
was too impatient.
The mantis stalks the cicada,
unaware of the oriole behind.
Now,
I see mantises and cicadas everywhere,
but the oriole is nowhere to be found.
Chief Batou ordered Shangguan Chengming's arrest.
We're not getting involved in this mess,
lest we get blindsided
by the oriole.
From the looks of it,
someone is trying to revolt.
Third Brother,
who do you think it could be?
Second Brother isn't ambitious.
He just wants a peaceful end.
He wouldn't do such a thing.
Fourth Brother thinks he's above it all,
so it definitely can't be him.
Could it be...
Eldest Brother?
Qin Baichuan?
He's been in Suhang for a long time,
so there's little news of him.
I wouldn't even know
where to begin guessing.
Then who do you think we should side with this time?
Side with whom?
At a time like this, we brothers should just
sit on the fence and see which way the wind blows.
Whichever way the wind blows...
The grass bends.
Third Brother.
Second Master,
I know you want a peaceful life now
and no longer wish to live by swindling.
But now that Sect Master is dead,
do you think the sect will know peace?
Someone
set a trap for Shangguan Chengming.
He won't
get out of this easily.
You came to me
instead of going to mourn
Sect Master.
You want me to help him, don't you?
Second Brother,
in the entire sect,
you were the most loyal to Sect Master.
But his death is shrouded
in mystery.
You and I
can't just let it go.
Just take care of yourself.
I just hope you can
fly higher
and further.
Mentor,
I've bought your ticket
to Pangzhou.
At this stage of the plan,
you can
leave the rest to me.
The 36 revolutions of the Kan and Li; yet there remains
the meeting of the Dragon and Tiger in the dantian.
This is the final hurdle.
Whether you can cross it
is in the hands of destiny.
Don't worry.
I've dug the graves for
the remaining few.
As your mentor,
I've taught you everything I know.
I'm getting old.
All I see
are old grudges.
But you can see very far.
Right now,
I just want Tianxiang Sect wiped from this world.
I don't want anyone else...
to get caught up in grudges like mine.
Mentor.
Please come in.
[Chunfeng House]
Come in.
You sure are bold to
run around when they are
hunting you down.
Now the sect is in chaos,
with Qin Baichuan in charge.
His ambition is no secret to anyone.
So what's your plan?
I've got my eye on a scam target.
He has the
inside information on Qin Baichuan's rebellion.
Do me a favor.
Go find him
and get the evidence.
Here are the address and the ticket.
[13 Wanping Road, Qiu Mansion, Pujiang]
Pujiang.
That's quite far.
What about you?
Staying here all alone,
what are you planning to do?
I'll be—
They're hunting you everywhere.
How about this?
You go find him.
It's a good chance
to lay low.
To take this throne, you're the first person
Qin Baichuan will try to eliminate.
You're the chief of Yuehaitang Branch,
which makes you his biggest threat.
It's not safe for you to stay here.
Shangguan Chengming,
so you're sending me away because you are
worried about my safety.
Then you can stay behind alone
and fight them all.
Right?
As you know...
until Tianxiang Sect is annihilated,
I'm staying right here—
♪ May you journey toward your future ♪
♪ Leave this stormy sea behind ♪
♪ Let the toxic love we shared ♪
♪ Be the moss that helps you grow ♪
♪ May you find your way out of the haze that is us ♪
♪ Leave me out of your story ♪
♪ Should freedom be your ultimate desire ♪
♪ I shall bloom for you in silence ♪
You said it yourself:
If you fear death, go home and rear pigs.
Since everyone is here,
we must allow Sect Master to rest in peace today.
Eldest Master,
don't you agree?
You're very thoughtful, Feiyan.
Now,
bring Shangguan Chengming in!
Jiang Feiyan,
you captured him.
The credit goes to you.
But it's not your place
to speak here.
Men,
drag him out and execute him!
Let's see who dares to lay a hand on him!
Since when does a woman
call the shots in Tianxiang Sect?
Tianxiang Sect has abandoned the fight for justice.
Does it matter if a woman is in charge?
Starting today,
whoever is most capable
will rule Tianxiang Sect!
So you want to be
the new sect master?
You got that right.
I want to be the sect master
and establish my own sect.
Come clean.
Who ordered you
to kill Sect Master?
Answer me!
Since you're throwing me under the bus,
I'll spill everything.
It was him,
Qin Baichuan.
He wanted me to pose as Sect Master's son
to get close to him,
gain his absolute trust, and then strike
when the moment was right!
Shangguan Chengming,
you're quite the strategist, huh?
It wasn't me who wanted Sect Master dead
but you and Jiang Feiyan!
In 1928,
Wang Jiaxian
and Jiang Feiyan
tied the knot.
I found this
from your hometown, Jianghuai.
One of you
pretended to be Sect Master's son
to poison him,
while the other covered it up
and joined the scam.
You haven't even wiped your own asses,
and you're trying to dump your feces on someone else?
Everyone,
what is the punishment
for treachery?
Human oil candle!
Yes, human oil candle!
Arrest Jiang Feiyan and Wang Jiaxian!
Treachery does warrant
the human oil candle punishment.
But it's still uncertain
who the real traitor is.
I have a piece of evidence here too.
Will you read it...
or will your son,
Qin Huiming, read it?
Go,
get us brothers another pot of wine.
Yes, Eldest Master.
How was it?
I eavesdropped outside the window for a long time,
but I heard nothing unusual.
They talked about protecting Sect Master's empire,
and Qin Baichuan told Second Master
to stay away
from Fifth Batou.
Qin Baichuan is threatening
Second Batou into
handing over Jiang Feiyan.
So he's the one who wants to revolt.
He bided his time
and finally got the chance.
Qin Baichuan wants to pull Second Batou to his side.
Then they're about to make a move.
Second Batou might not necessarily join his sinking ship.
But I bet
Qin Baichuan has a backup plan.
During their conversation,
a gofer was there the whole time.
Why wasn't Qin Baichuan
worried about the gofer hearing such secrets?
Qin Baichuan probably wanted the gofer to hear it.
Where's that gofer?
It's been forever,
and still, nobody has
touched base with him.
How about I just
grab him here?
A few punches
and he'll talk.
Catching him is easy.
If Qin Baichuan
secures proof of our rebellion,
we're dead either way.
Why are
the mosquitoes only biting me and not you?
I'll follow him.
You go to the river
and see if he left anything behind.
Stay put. I'll go.
If his contact shows up,
I can handle them.
Okay.
Brothers,
Sect Master is dead.
Before the funeral altar,
burning incense is the signal.
Raise the banner of justice,
revolt, and seize the sect.
From Qin Huiming.
Eldest Master,
you're truly blessed in this life.
You actually have a son.
Why didn't you tell everyone?
Do you think you can sling mud
with a fake letter?
How is it that your photos are real
but my evidence is fake?
Besides,
he is right here.
We'll know the truth
once we test it.
Enough!
Shangguan Chengming,
you deceived Sixth Batou,
killed Sect Master,
and dragged Feiyan into danger with you.
Isn't that enough?
Now you're here falsely
accusing Chief Batou!
Second Master,
you've followed Sect Master for so long.
You wouldn't want him to roll over
in his grave, would you?
Eldest Master,
it's simple.
Trade this gofer's life...
to prove your innocence.
Eldest Master.
Okay,
I'll help you.
He is my son!
I'm...
I'm revolting today!
I've already deployed my men.
Zhou is already dead!
The position of Sect Master
belongs to me, Qin Baichuan!
Eldest Master!
Freeze! Drop your knives!
Where did you come from?
The men you placed in ambush
outside the city were
all wiped out by me.
You...
Interesting.
How interesting.
I've attended many funerals in my life,
but attending my own
is a first.
Quick, go brew some alum soup
to detoxify me.
Careful, Master.
I'll go right away.
You're here.
Yes, I'm here.
What are all those people waiting for outside?
Waiting for me to die.
Come on.
You've worked hard all these years.
Let me pour you a cup of tea.
Thank you, Master.
Drink up.
Is your family doing well?
Yes,
they're good.
I know you have 3 kids.
Are your finances okay?
Yes,
you've always been generous.
When things ease up,
take a trip home.
Spend some quality time with your wife and kids.
It's been a while since you went back, right?
Thank you, Master.
Over the years...
Don't worry.
I'll take good care of your family for you.
No one can leave the premises
until Sect Master comes out.
Senior?
Senior!
Somebody come quickly!
Senior?
Senior!
What happened to Sect Master?
Sect Master!
Master!
Senior,
trust that I'll avenge you.
I promise.
S-Sect...
Sect Master?
Qin,
if you want my throne,
just say it.
Why go to such lengths?
You knew he was Wang Jiaxian,
but you kept mum,
so as to use him to do your dirty work.
Director Wang,
what punishment does this call for?
The father and son, Qin Baichuan and Qin Huiming,
defrauded the people and committed murder for money.
They deserve to die.
Death penalty.
Execute them on the spot.
Take them away!
Wait.
Let me say one thing before you go.
As things stand,
this is where we part ways, my brother.
There's nothing else I can do for you.
Tell you what,
I'll pay for the bullets to execute you.
Director Wang,
buy a few more bullets.
That's a lot.
Take him away.
You old fox!
You'll meet a dreadful end!
I'll haunt you from the grave!
You old fox!
You'll die a horrible death!
Director Wang,
since you're here,
have a cup of tea before you go.
I have official business to handle,
so I won't stay.
Let's catch up another day.
Another day.
Just one shot?
Give it a second.
Satisfying.
All done.
Thank you.
I'll take my leave.
Wang Jiaxian,
right?
I set the scene
perfectly for you.
How did you mess it up like this?
I'll get to the point.
Tomorrow at Yunhe Temple,
Wang Jiaxian and Jiang Feiyan will be subjected to
the human oil candle punishment.
Do it the old way,
full scale and by the book.
You guys, keep a close eye on them.
Yes!
Shangguan Chengming and Jiang Feiyan
both played themselves.
What a ruthless move
from Sect Master.
By feigning dead,
he not only rooted out these two traitors,
but even got rid of Qin Baichuan,
the long-standing threat.
Brilliant.
Absolutely brilliant.
Third Brother,
now only Second Brother
is above you.
And Sect Master
told us to handle
the human oil candle punishment well.
Why do you think
that is?
Sect Master has run out of
competent people he can trust.
Our chance has come.
Have some tea.
Master,
you raised Feiyan yourself.
She's basically half a daughter to you.
Please spare her life.
The tea is cold.
Go get some boiling water.
Master,
Feiyan has worked
tirelessly for the sect all these years.
Her efforts alone deserve credit.
Think of how much money she's made for us.
It's not worth
losing one of our Batous
over that punk, Master!
I know you have a soft spot for her
and can't bear to see her die.
I don't have the heart to either.
I want to spare her too,
but the rules are the rules.
I understand.
A life for a life.
What's with this act now?
I think you've watched too many plays, trying to be
the knight in shining armor.
Listen up.
Those stories are
made up by actors to sell tickets.
Those are performances!
Life only begins after
you step off the stage.
Feiyan's time is up.
She must die.
It's not a decision I made.
It's arranged by heaven.
You want to help her?
Fine.
Make your strike accurate.
Give her a quick end
so she suffers less.
Just like how I killed Shangguan Hong with my own hands back then.
Huaiyi,
transcend romantic attachments,
and you'll be king.
Understood.
♪ There is a fiery woman in the brothel ♪
Feiyan,
back then,
you used to warm up your voice
and practice
in this courtyard.
I was so hopeless back then.
I always liked to
secretly watch you
from afar.
Just watching
and watching...
Until the day I saw you
put on the makeup,
step onto the stage,
and win the applause of the whole house.
I can no longer protect you anymore.
Remember,
you must fly higher...
and go
further.
I'll just say a few words.
Fourth Brother.
Chengming,
it was a pleasure knowing you.
You'll be on your way tomorrow.
Let's have a drink
as my farewell to you.
Fourth Brother,
you're putting yourself in danger
by visiting me.
Don't worry.
In Tianxiang Sect, I alone master Western knowledge.
Sect Master can't afford to kill me.
I just hate myself for
not being able to save you.
Fourth Brother,
please do me one last favor.
Fourth Master,
Sect Master ordered
that no one who's seen Shangguan Chengming
is allowed to leave.
With the war intensifying outside,
word has come down from the top
that Yucheng is now our official rear base.
With this decree,
the military and police systems
in Yucheng have undergone multiple purges.
It's recent: the deputy director
from headquarters,
his name and identity are all kept secret.
No one knows a thing.
My words don't carry
as much weight as they used to.
It's hard enough
to protect myself, let alone help a friend out.
Times are tough
for everyone right now.
But times like these are exactly when
we buddies should help each other out.
Tell you what,
I'll give you an extra 10% cut
from Tianxiang Sect's business—
make life a little easier for you, bud.
Truth be told,
you're talking about Tianxiang Sect's internal affairs,
something a guy in uniform like me can't get involved in.
Then I'll add another 10%.
How does that sound?
You're truly a master of calculation.
It's all thanks to you that
I get to stick around in Yucheng.
[Sever the Heavenly Light]
Heaven hides no evil,
and earth harbors no filth.
Wang Jiaxian and Jiang Feiyan have
violated the sect rules
and shall be subjected
to the human oil candle punishment.
Cleansing Matron.
Proceed.
Yes.
Today, we have rebellious disciples
who disrupted our sect's order.
Kill them! Kill them!
First, we invite the past sect masters
to witness your crime of betraying the sect!
Kill them! Kill them!
Second, we invite our fellow disciples
to jointly execute you for your treachery.
Kill them! Kill them!
Third, I summon the disciplinary artifacts
to chastise you renegades!
Kill them! Kill them!
The time has come.
Execute them.
[In the next episode]
Haven't you been dying to kill me?
Come on.
I'll grant your wish.
What a rare guest.
Do you need something?
Yes.
What is it?
A life exchange.
Are you done living?
Long ago.
Deal.
How do you want to die?
I get to choose?
Sure.
You're so ruthless.
Not as evil as you.
Let me tell you something.
You've met the real Shangguan Chengming.